<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Development on alextrandafir blog</title>
    <link>/blog/categories/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Development on alextrandafir blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 17:44:57 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/blog/categories/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing My First Swift App</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/writing-my-first-swift-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 17:44:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/writing-my-first-swift-app/</guid>
      <description>This post is not intended to be a tutorial on how to write your first app. It&#39;s merely my experience and maybe a general guideline on what to expect if you&#39;re trying to do this for the first time. If you already wrote an IOS app this post is probably not for you. I&#39;ve always considered that, in order to become better at something, you need to explore the surroundings. IT has a lot of sub-fields and, for a developer, the simplest way to explore is to play around with a new language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fear of Production</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/fear-of-production/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 09:47:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/fear-of-production/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve stumbled upon this two times with personal projects and numerous times at work. It&#39;s a weird feeling that, even though you know you&#39;ve done all the right things, keeps you from going into production. I can&#39;t really talk much about work related stuff. However I can say that, even though we do all our testing within our teams, even though we have entire departments responsible with regression testing, even though we have very good incident management procedures, very good customer care services, very good infrastructure department, I still sometimes had a weird vibe regarding going into production.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>